So some time ago you
saw a video on our channel, we decoded the annual report of IADA,
we talked about the claim ratio,
we
talked about the health insurance industry, but
your answer is always that you have told us
that this health insurance industry is
working in this way, but
which health
insurance policy is good for me and my family, so for that
we have brought a comparison for you, Top
Six Health Insurance Companies of 2025, stay
till the end of the video, there
is a detailed comparison, in the end we
will also share the premium with you, so that you can decide
which plan is good for your family,
before starting the video, I would
like to introduce myself, my name is
Gurleen Ka Tikku, I am a Certified
Financial Planner, I have been
associated with the insurance industry for the last 20 years
and every week I bring videos for you so that
your insurance bank
journey becomes easy and happy because the
tagline of our company is Creating a Wealth
of Happiness, let's move towards the video, Top
Six Health  Insurance Companies of 2025: The
companies we are comparing here
are
Neeva B Health Aspire Plan, ADAC Argo
Optima Secure Plan, ICS Lombard
Elevate Base Plan, Aditya Birla Active One
Max Plan, Manipal Cigna Sarvaha Param
Plan and Care Health's Supreme Plan. So,
we will talk about these plans in detail.
What are the features of these plans, what are the
eligibility criteria, who can take
these plans, what are the similarities in these plans,
what is the comparison, and lastly, we will
talk about the premium. So, first we will
talk about ICR which is Income Claim Ratio.
Income Claim Ratio is basically
how much money came to the insurance company
and how many
claims it has. IR
is 59.01 for hdfcergo.com,
78.8 for Aditya Birla, 68.3
for Manipal Cigna, ICR is 63.7 and
ICR of Care Health is 57.6. This is the latest
IADA report.  First let's talk about
USP, what is the USP in which plan,
which plan sells the most for what, the
biggest USP in Sova B Aspire is
Lock the Clock, which means your premium gets locked till
the time you make your first
claim, your
premium remains locked till you make the claim, it gets locked at the current age,
only age gets locked, inflation is
not locked, keep in mind, secondly in this plan
borderless means your global cover
is also included, if you want to get treatment outside India, then you
can take borderless rider and you
can get treatment outside, third is maternity cover,
maternity is basically covered under a miracle benefit
where pay newborn baby
expenses, adoption,
surrogacy, IVF, so basically the complete package
of motherhood is covered in this policy after a
waiting period of nine months, next is
booster plus benefit, which means what ever you do not
use is carried forward to the next
year, whatever time you do not use today will be
carried forward to the next year and
maximum  It will go up to 10 times. It
depends on the age at which you are
entering the policy. According to the multiplier
benefit, you get the booster benefit. It will go up
to a maximum of 10 times. If you have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh and
you have not used it, it will increase every year up
to 10 times, up to Rs 1 crore,
depending on your age. Next is
disease management rider. Disease management
rider gives you the option to cover
your BP and diabetes from day one. So
you have that option. If you already have
BP and diabetes, then
you can get that cover by taking the disease management rider. Now coming to
hdfcfund.com,
plus benefit. You are respectful of
claim center
hdfc0000088. After 3 years, when you renew,
you are eligible for 4x cover.
You are paying premium for 1x
but you are enjoying cover up to 3x and 4x.
Next is higher claim
ratio which is applicable on these claims.  Ratio
approximates
one of the parameters due to which
people opt for ADAC. Next is the IIC
Lombard Elevate plan. So here it was
launched only last year. The plan has some
features which are a little different from the market
like firstly Power Booster where your
sum insured will keep increasing by 100% every year up
to infighting. There is no maximum limit at all.
If you take Power Booster then
your sum insured is Rs. 10 lakhs. Next year 20-30 lakhs
and there is no upper limit. There is
no maximum limit. It will keep increasing for as many
years you are continuing the policy and
you have added Power Booster add-on.
Secondly, you get CIBIL discount. If
you maintain good CIBIL then
CIBIL discount is available. Thirdly, there is
another unique feature in IIC Lombard Elevate plan which is called
Infighting.
Once the claim for infighting comes,
you will get the full amount in the policy lifetime. Under
Infighting,
what will happen if there is more claim?
Fourth USP is that it is unlimited.  Sum assured
is available, so your sum assured option is
available up to unlimited, we
say 5 lakh, 10 lakh, 20, 25, 50, 1 crore,
2 crore, 3 crore. Here, unlimited sum
assured is available, you can choose that option
if you feel that in future the
expenses may increase a lot and
you want that satisfactorily
measured coverage, you can also opt for it and
many add-ons are available so because the
new plans that are coming, IADA is
bringing many add-ons so that you can
choose as per your convenience, so many
add-ons are also available in IIC Lord Elevate,
next is Aditya Bilal Active and
Max, its biggest USP is that here
you can take chronic care rider for some of your conditions, some of which are
asthma, BP, cholesterol,
diabetes, heart related conditions, obesity,
COPD, which can be covered from day one by
adding a  Rider. Another USP is that
you get super credit, which
is an inbuilt feature. You will get 100% sum assured
increase next year, maximum up to
500. This is relative to the claim.
If you buy the policy today, next year it will increase by 100%, maximum up to
5x.
Next is the Param plan from Moneypal Cigna Sarvaha.
It has three variants: Uttam, Param, and Pratham. So
today we will talk about these and
we are comparing Param.
Param is basically a no-
waiting period plan. There is no waiting
period in it, neither your initial waiting
period, nor specific exclusions, nor
your waiting period for pre-existing diseases.
So this is a no-waiting period plan.
Another USP of this plan is that it has
many riders available. Seven to eight
riders are available which you can use
with this plan to
make it more comprehensive. It is a very
comprehensive plan and to
make it comprehensive  78 riders are also
available for this. Lastly, we will talk about the
USP of Care Health Supreme Plan. It is Super
NCB which means your cover goes up to 7x.
Every year your cover will increase by 100%. This is an add-
on optional rider which you choose and the
cover goes up to a maximum of 7x and does
not reduce even if a claim comes. The
second USP is that instant cover is
available here for pre-existing conditions. There are
some pre-existing conditions for
which you can avail instant cover
by paying additional premium. Now let's talk about
room rent eligibility. There is
no room rent capping in NCB. You can
opt for any room
[praise]
to the same extent. Room rent
modification option is also available here which is an
add-on. If you want to upgrade to any room
or downgrade to twin sharing
basis room,
both options are available. Your premium will
increase and decrease
respectively.  There is
no room rung capping in the Care Health Supreme plan. You can
opt for any room. Now let's talk about the
eligibility criteria. The minimum entry
age for an adult in Niva Bupa Aspire is
18 years. The maximum entry age is currently 65
years. The minimum entry age for dependent
children is 91 days and the maximum is 30 years.
In GFC R Optima Secure, the
minimum entry age is 18 years with no
limit. You can enter this policy at any age. The
minimum entry age for dependent children is 91 days
and the maximum is 25 years. In ISI Lombard
Elevate, the minimum entry age is 18 years and the maximum is
125 years. Basically, there is no maximum
entry age limit for children. The
minimum
entry age for dependent children is 91 days and the maximum is 30 years.
In MoneyPlus Cigna Sarvaha Param plan, there is 18
years to no limit for adults.  Minimum age is
18 years and maximum age can be any.
You can enter in Pace policy. Dependent
children can stay in the policy from 91 days to 30 years.
Also,
in Care Supreme, minimum
entry age is 18 years for adult and maximum no
limit. Dependent children
can stay in the policy from 91 days to 24 years. Having said that,
life long renewability option
is available in all these six plans. After a point, you can renew your policy for life
long. The company will
not refuse you to renew till the
time you are paying the premium and you have
not done any fraudulent activity, then
you can renew for life long. In all the
policies, minimum term short term is
3 lakh in Niva Aspire and maximum is 1 crore.
HDFC0000082 Unlimited option is also available.
7 lakh to
6 crore in Aditya Bella Active plan and 5 lakh to 6 crore in Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha Param
plan.  Lakh to 3 Crore
Options from Rs 5 Lakh to 1 Crore are available in Care Supreme
Policy Tenor All policies
are available for one year, two year, three year If you
take a long tenure policy, that is, if you
take a policy of 2 years, three years, then the company
gives you additional discounts when you pay
upfront premium for 2 years and 3
years So all these options are available in all six
plans Bonus Bonus is basically
something the company is incentivizing you
if you do not take a claim or is
giving a loyalty addition, so all of them are different, let
us see what all are there So
in B Aspire plan, there is a
bonus called Booster Plus, so
in Booster Plus you have different variants Gold
Plus is the starting category, then the
Diamond Plus, then Platinum Plus and
Titanium Plus So
what was the booster of B that if you do not
take a claim, then the balance will always be carried forward
and maximum limits were defined, so
your super credit in hdfc0cpdccb LA Active One Max  The
benefit is 100% in
the first year and then Rs. 200 in the next year. This is
also a kind of loyalty addition. The maximum amount will
go up to Rs. 500. The Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha plan has
a piggy bank benefit which is a guaranteed
increase of 100% sum assured every year.
Whatever your sum assured is today, it will
increase by 100% next year. Its respective maximum
claim will go up to 10 times, up to 10
times. In the Care Supreme plan,
you get a bonus on Rs. 50, maximum up to
100%. There will be no reduction in case of any
future claim. Day care treatments
are covered in all the plans. There is
no short list of all specified day
care procedures. Then AISH
hospitalization AISH is basically Ayurveda,
Yoga, Unani, Siddha, Homeopathy. Its
hospitalization is also covered
in the policies. Up to 10 times short domicile
hospitalization, such hospitalization, yes,
going to the hospital is possible.  No, there are two conditions, the
patient is not in a condition to go to the
hospital, secondly,
beds are not available in the hospitals, so the
treatment of domicile hospitalization
is also covered in these six plans, up to sum, organ donation
and transplant expenses are also covered,
costs up to harvesting are covered
in all these policies, up to sum shared refill
benefit, so refill benefit, restore benefit,
reinstatement benefit are used with different names,
so this is basically a benefit,
suppose your sum shared is exhausted,
you have used it in one year, now
what for the remaining members, or what if you are
hospitalized again, then the
refill benefit gets triggered, like
in Niva Bupa, Reassure For, your
refill gets triggered only after you have made the first claim,
for example, if you have a policy of Rs 10 lakh,
you have used it completely in one year,
then Rs 10 lakh will be refilled again
which can be utilized for  Subsequent
claim number of times
Number of times equal to base sum Short
Aditya Birla Active One also
offers unlimited number of times for any person,
any illness Money Plan Cigna Sarvaha plan offers
100% of sum assured multiple times,
meaning unlimited number of times are
available for related, unrelated, same person,
different person All are covered
Same goes for Care Health Supreme also
offers unlimited refill benefit without any restriction
Emergency Road
Ambulance So, road ambulance
expenses are covered in Niva Bupa Aspire
Age per actuals,
whatever the expenses are, you are reimbursed
HDFC Rogo also offers Age per actuals
ICSC Lombard Elevate Base Plan
also offers Age per actuals Aditya Birla
Active One Max Age per actuals
Manpal Cigna Sarvaha Plan also Age per
actuals covered up to base sum A Shared Care
Health Supreme Plan  If you have a
policy of less than 15 lakhs, then road
ambulance charges up to ₹1000000 will be covered. If your policy is above 15 lakhs,
then up to sum assured emergency
air ambulance is covered in Niva Bappa Spire. The
actual expense on the age is
given. This is
not available in Aditya Badla Active and Max. You
can also add rider in Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha Param plan.
Maximum limit is ₹10 lakh. Care Health
Supreme plan has an optional rider.
Air ambulance up to ₹10 lakh can be covered.
Annual health checkup: So annual health checkup is
included in your policies. In NV Air, it
is included up to ₹1000000 and it is
on cashless basis. You have to
book the test through their application only. Next, it depends on
your sum assured. In ISI Lord
Elevate plan, the age is cashless.
You will be given a cover as per your sum assured as per the list. Aditya
Once a year benefit is available in Bedla Active One Max.
Once a year benefit is also available in Money Pal Signal Sarvaha plan.
Annual health checkup and once a year benefit is
also available in Aapka Care Health Supreme for
all insured members. Pre and post
hospitalization expenses, that is,
expenses before going to the hospital and
expenses after going to the hospital will also be reimbursed,
which is related to the hospitalization.
Suppose
you consulted a doctor before getting admitted, got some
diagnostic tests done, took some
medicines and got hospitalized on that basis, then
you can get all those expenses reimbursed. And while
going home from the hospital, the doctor told you some post
hospitalization that you will
take some medicines and will also get physiotherapy done,
so all that is covered up to the same shot.
So in Niva Bupa, it is 60 days pre and 180 days
post hospitalization. Your
HDFC Ergo Secure also has 60 days
pre and 180 days post hospitalization cover.
90 days pre and 180 days post hospitalization
expenses are covered in Aditya Birla ISI Lombard
90 days pre and 180 days post
hospitalization expenses are covered in
Aditya Birla Active One Max 90
days pre and 180 days post expenses are
covered in Manipal Cigna also 90 days
pre and 180 days post expenses are covered in Air Health Supreme
plan 60 days pre and 180 days post expenses are
covered so this is on re-
imbursement basis e-consultation so e-
consultation is included in your policy
Niva Bappa Aspire has unlimited e-
consultation covered and
you can take second medical opinion once in a year E-consultation is available
in ADAC Ergo Optima Secure
for 51 listed
critical illnesses
Unlimited e-consultation is also available in ISC Lombard Elevate
This feature is available in Aditya Birla.
Unlimited e-consultation is available in the Money Pal
Cigna Sarvaha plan and unlimited
consultation through general physician is covered
in the Care Supreme plan. Modern
treatments and robotic surgeries,
also known as advanced procedures, are also covered in the
IADA list published on the Edge. All these
are covered up to the sum share.
This is your limit up to the sum share. You will be
covered up to the amount of your sum share on the
Edge. Actually, let's
talk about
wellness benefits in all these plans. Wellness benefits are
basically those through which you get some additional
wellness benefits. Your wellness is
also focused on. Either you
walk daily steps, you
get some points for that, which
gives you a discount on the premium, or you
get some such offers which you can avail. You can get
tests done from LETS, you
can buy medicines at a lower price, at a
discounted price.  Wellness
benefits are different in different policies.
Niva Spire has Live Healthy benefit.
You are eligible for a discount of up to 30% on the number of steps you walk
at the time of renewal. In
Care Health Supreme plan,
you also get a discount of up to 30% on
consultation, diagnostics, and their
network. If you consult a doctor,
these discounts are available to you.
Non-payable items are
inbuilt in some policies, in some you have to add
on. One non-payable item is
consumable items, PP kits, masks,
gloves, these are not included in your policy.
So, riders are available for non-payable items in Niva Spire,
Safeguard
and Safeguard Plus. Now you can add that rider
to cover your non-payable items fully. The
other hdfcergo.com
is included in which your 68 listed non-
payable items are covered.
You can add a rider in ISI Lord Elevate.  There is what is called
claim protector which will cover your non-
payable items then next comes
Aditya Birla Active One Max here it
is inbuilt 147 listed items
are covered for your non-payable items then comes your Money
Pal Cigna Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha Param
plan here there is a rider for non-medical expenses and
durable medical expenses
which you can add which covers your policy due to which
non-payable items are
covered similarly there is claim
shield rider in Care Supreme which you
can add to cover your non-payable items
OPD cover so OPD is an add on which you
can add in your policies Niva and Aspire have
well consult benefit for OPD
you can add it after looking at the additional premium
so keep in mind that OPD is on cashless basis
so for OPD
you have to go through their network mainly it is on cashless basis
some reimbursement options are also available
with co-payment but their network
You have to consult through this only and then you
can avail cashless treatment. The network of OPD is
different from your cashless
hospital network. So here the network of doctors
is different where you can consult.
So for OPD cover, you can add well consult rider.
You share some amount in the claim every time.
Suppose if you have a copayment of Rs. 10, then
you will have to pay Rs. 10 in every claim. So,
such an option is not available in Niva Bappa
Aspire and also not in ADAC Ergo Optima
Secure.
You can add copayment in ICA Lombard Elevate. It is
not available in Aditya Birla Active One Max. You can add copayment in Money Pal Signal Sarvaha plan
to reduce your
premium. Same goes for Care Health. There is no
OPD there, there is no copayment
and no payment option.
Deductible is deductible, annual aggregate
deductible or per day deductible also. That one
is specifically available in Money Pal Cigna.  The
amount you will pay upfront
before the policy kicks in. So, deductible
option is available in Niva Bupa Expire
where you can reduce your premium
by opting for a small deductible.
Deductible is also available in ADAC, Cargo, Optima Secure.
Deductible is not available in IIC Lord Elevate. Deductible is not available in Aditya Bill
Active One.
Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha Param plan
also has deductible, aggregate deductible and per
day deductible, so you can choose.
Premium gets reduced accordingly.
Deductible is not available in Ker Hel Supreme.
Now let's talk about waiting period.
So, what are the waiting periods?
Initial waiting period in these policies means
you cannot make a claim immediately after taking the policy. There is some
cooling off period. So, the initial
waiting period is 30 days in all these plans.
Except in Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha Param plan
because it is a no waiting period
plan, there is no  There is no waiting period,
then we will talk about specific exclusion
waiting period which is the waiting period for slow growing illness,
which is listed, there are
some diseases which by default will
not be covered for 2 years, that waiting period is
also not applicable in Money Pal Cigna,
but in all other policies it is of two years or 24
months and then we will talk about pre-
existing diseases waiting period, these are those
things which you already have before taking the policy,
so you will have to serve some waiting period for it,
so for example, if we talk about
Niva Bupa Aspire, there is a
waiting period of four years in Gold Plus.  There is a waiting period for pre-
existing diseases and in Diamond Platinum and
Titanium there is a waiting period of three years
for pre-existing conditions.
In HDFC Ergo Optima Secure there is a waiting
period of three years for pre-
existing conditions. In ICAC Lord Elevate
also there is a waiting period of 36 months for pre-existing diseases.
Some riders are
available here like Niva Bupa Aspire has
Disease Management Rider by which you can get
covered after 30 days for your pre-
existing condition BP and Diabetes. Similarly,
Jump Start is available in ICAC Labd. There are
A B C D O conditions which
are Asthma, BP, Cholesterol, Diabetes and
Obesity or you can get it covered after 30 days
by opting for Jump Start Rider
hdfcergo.com
conditions can be covered from day one which are
Asthma, BP, Cholesterol, Diabetes,
Obesity, Heart Related Conditions
and COPD. In Mani Pulse Sagan Sarvaha Plan
as we said that  There is
no waiting period for pre-exit conditions. Also,
Instant Cover
Rider is available in the Supreme plan to cover your pre-existing
diseases from day one. So, Instant Cover also has
AB/CD conditions like Asthma,
BP, Cholesterol and Diabetes, which you
can get covered after 30 days by opting
for Instant Care Rider.
We have talked about waiting periods. Let us
talk about some additional features to see
which ones are covered and which ones are not. For example, maternity
expenses are
covered in your Niva Bupa Aspire. There is a waiting period of 48 months in Gold,
24 months in Diamond and
nine months in Platinum and Titanium.
Maternity is not covered in ADFC ARG Optima Secure.
Maternity and newborn baby coverage is also available in ICICI Lombard Elevate. There is
no maternity cover in Aditya Birla Active One. There is a Money Pal in both the other plans as well.
Maternity is not covered in Cigna Sarvaha Param and CareHealth Supreme, nor is the
rider available. Global cover is available. So,
basically, if you
want to get treatment outside India, then global cover
is available. Borderless Endava Bupa Aspire.
Payment options are also available in this. If you are
not taking hdfcfund.com, then
you will get a cash back, which is the feature called
cash bag, you will get it in your wallet. 10%
off your premium in the first year, after that 5%
off your premium. You can use this to
pay your renewal premium
or if there is any OPD expense,
you can get it covered too. After that, there is
borderless which is your worldwide cover.
Then there is future ready. If you want future
guarantee of adding your spouse from
today itself, then that option
is available. Fast forward, if you pay the premium for 2 years or 3 years
together, then you can enjoy 2 years and 3
years cover together. Then
Safeguard and Safeguard Plus are
related to non-payable items. Hospital Daily  Cash
benefit means
you will be given daily cash benefit for the number of days you are hospitalized. PA is
Personal Accidental which covers your
accidental death and disability benefit.
Smart Health Rider, the disease management
rider we are talking about,
is available through which your BP and diabetes can be covered by the device.
Well Consult, which is your
OPD rider. Now let's talk about
hdfcergo.com. The term
Hospital Cash means you will be given daily cash benefit for the number of days you are
hospitalized. Then there is
Critical Illness, for which a lump sum payout will be given in
case any critical illness is diagnosed. Then there
is IPA which is Individual Personal
Accidental, in which accidental death and
disability are covered. Permanent
Disability, then there is your Optima Well Being, which
is your rider for OPD. The
riders of ICICI Lombard are
on the screen in front of you. The durable medical
equipment you want to cover is
dependent accommodation.  The benefit is annual
health check up. Through a rider, you
can add a protector to cover your non-payable
items. Power Booster, through which your 100% sum
assured keeps increasing every year. There is
no maximum limit.
Inflation can be under-inflated.
You can also avail ambulance cover. Then there is the
network advantage. Tiered
network is also available in ANV Air. You can also choose a rider for tiered network.
You get a discount through it
if you are going on a tiered network,
but if you go somewhere else,
you will have to pay 20% there. Then there is
Nursing at Home Compassionate
Inflation Protector. All these benefits are
available, which you can opt for if you want.
Then coming to Aditya
Birla, Chronic Care is available here
which covers your ABCD Plus conditions
from day one. And the second is your room
category if you want to reduce
from a nine room to a single room.  If you want,
you can use this rider. Reduce the
room category is room modification. Basically,
in the Money Pal Cigna Sarvaha plan,
some riders are available and some are not. There are a lot of
riders in the Sarvaha Param plan. The first one is
Pratiksha. As you know, there is no
waiting period in it, neither for slow
growing illness nor for pre-exit condition. Pratiksha is
basically you are
adding the waiting period. You know, you do
not have any pre-existing condition. The
premium of the plan is usually higher because
you are covered from day one. So you should add
Pratiksha, add
waiting period yourself and your premium will reduce. If
you do not have any pre-existing condition,
then adding waiting period is a good
idea. Second, Surplus Benefit: You will get additional 100%
of sum assured from the first year. On the first
claim of each policy year, you will get additional 100%
benefit added in the form of
surplus. There is also personal accidental cover.
You can add from Rs. 1 lakh to 3 crore.
Then there is coverage for non-medical expenses
and durable medical expenses. You can also get this
covered by taking and on air
ambulance. Room rank modification on any room or
twin sharing basis. You can choose the option of
voluntary copayment or
voluntary deductible. Both
options are available. Next is Care Health
Supreme Plan. It has a rider which is
called NCB Super in which you will get 100%
sum assured every year. Maximum
goes up to Rs. 500. Second is Instant Cover
where your hypertension, diabetes, asthma,
cholesterol etc. are covered after 30 days.
Then second is Modification of PD
Wait Period. If you want to extend the three year plan to two years
or one year, then you
can choose this rider. Then there is Claim Shield.
Non-payable items are covered in Claim Shield.
Another rider is Be Fit
where you can access your gyms unlimited number
of times.  It should be in one year and
above 12 years. Let us
talk about discounts. What discounts are available in these plans? The
first discount in np Aspire plan is Long Tenure
Discount. This means if you take a policy for 2 years or 3 years
together, then you are given a discount.
Second is if you are adding more than one
individual in one policy
under multi-individual option, then
you are given a family discount of 10%, then
standing instruction discount which is
2.5%. If you have set up auto debit, then you will
get 2.5% discount. There is Live Healthy
Discount which is up to 30% and
if you are a doctor or medical practitioner,
then you can avail 5% discount in Niva Boop Spire. There
is a discount of 10% and there is a loyalty discount
if you go to hdfcergo.com,
Secure, ICI, Lord, Elevate. You are
given CIBIL discount and one
is your Long Tenure Discount. If you take a policy for 2 years or 3 years
together, then you
get a discount.  You can do this and there is an early renewal
discount if you renew your policy before 30 days
then there is 2.5% early
renewal discount and along with that there is
also a wellness benefit discount of up to 30 days.
In Aditya Birla Active One Max you
get a discount on health returns which is up to
100% and along with that there is a long term
discount that if you pay the premium of 2 years or 3 years
together then you
get a discount. Some discounts are also available in Money Pal Cigna
which are in
front of you on your screen, you can check them. The
discounts in Care Supreme are also mentioned
on your sheet, you
can check them. So these are the details about all these
six plans. Now we will talk about the premium,
how much will the premium actually be charged, the
premium is on your screen. So the
premium that we have taken is for
both Jan N and Jan 2, here and the family has taken a
family of three (31+28) and the age is 2+
1, family size two adults and one child,
cover of Rs 10 lakh has been taken and  We have taken the premium with consumer bill.
In many plans it
is inbuilt, we have included consumer at some places like it
is inbuilt in ADAC Cargo, it
is inbuilt in Aditya Birla Active One, in the rest
we have included consumer rider. Because in our opinion,
consumer bill rider is a must,
you should take it because otherwise at the time of claim there are
some expenses which are non-
payable items which are up to 10%
part of your claim amount,
so it is necessary to take consumer bill. You can see this
premium on your screen of Jan One Jan Two.
Detailed visual videos of all these plans are also
available. Do your due diligence and
read about these plans carefully. If
you want to take it, watch the detailed videos and
refer. If you want to connect,
connect with our team. They will also
assist you in buying health
insurance policy.
whatsapp-web that's
[music]